Go get the room key card.
Ambilkan kunci kamar.
Brother Huiming.
Kakak Hui Ming.
Be gentle, you're hurting me.
Pelan sedikit, kau menyakitiku.
Isn't that Miss Liu's voice?
Bukankah ini suara Nona Liu?
Why does it sound like she's calling Young Master Ying?
Kenapa kedengarannya seperti sedang memanggil Tuan Muda Ying?
Young Master Ying's official girlfriend is still here.
Tuan Ying, pacar asli masih ada di sini.
Could it be...
Jangan-jangan
This...
Ini...
That's enough.
Cukup.
Aunt Mu.
Bibi Mu.
No matter what kind of misunderstanding is happening inside,
Tidak peduli kesalahpahaman seperti apa yang terjadi di sana,
it's not appropriate for so many people to gather here.
Tidak pantas bagi banyak orang untuk mengepung tempat ini.
Miss Lin.
Nona Lin,
You must think so too, right?
Seharusnya kau juga merasa begitu, 'kan?
Since it's a misunderstanding,
Karena ini adalah kesalahpahaman,
it should be cleared up in front of everyone.
Tentu saja harus diselesaikan di depan umum.
Let everyone see
Biarkan semua orang melihat
who is making such a commotion with Liu Yinyin inside.
Siapa sebenarnya yang membuat
Who exactly it is.
Sebenarnya siapa?
Huiming.
Hui Ming.
What do you think?
Menurutmu?
Why are you here?
Kenapa kau ada di sini?
I'm not here.
Aku tidak di sini.
Where did Aunt Lu think I was?
Bibi Lu kira aku ada di mana?
I wasn't feeling well just now.
Tadi aku agak tidak enak badan.
I stepped out from the banquet to get some air.
Aku keluar dari pesta untuk mencari udara segar.
Then...
Kalau begitu...
Who's inside then?
Jadi siapa yang ada di dalam?
The room key card is here.
Kartu kamar sudah datang.
Get out.
Pergi
Why is it you?
Kenapa malah kau?
Miss Liu, how can you act like this?
Nona Liu, kenapa kau seperti ini?
Just now, you clearly said
Tadi jelas-jelas kau yang bilang
that you couldn't control your feelings for me.
Tidak bisa mengendalikan perasaanku
Get out!
Pergi sana!
What nonsense are you talking about?
Omong kosong apa?
You're just a waiter.
Kau seorang pelayan,
How could my daughter possibly like you?
Bagaimana putriku bisa menyukaimu?
Someone, come!
Pengawal.
Take him back to the Lu family for punishment.
Bawa dia ke Keluarga Lu untuk ditangani.
Nobody move!
Jangan ada yang bergerak.
What's going on?
Ada apa?
Is this matter just going to end like this?
Masalah ini selesai begitu saja?
You all thought the person inside was me just now.
Kalian tadi mengira orang yang ada di dalam adalah aku.
I have to give my fiancée an explanation.
Aku harus memberikan penjelasan kepada tunanganku
Take him to the police station.
Bawa dia ke kantor polisi.
If we don't find out the truth,
Tidak menyelidiki kebenarannya,
I won't let this go.
Tidak akan menyerah.
Huiming
Hui Ming.
You grew up together with Yinyin.
Kau tumbuh besar bersama Yinyin.
You can't just stand by and watch her be humiliated.
Kau tidak bisa melihat dia malu, 'kan?
If I had known it would turn out like this,
Jika tahu seperti ini,
why did we even bother in the first place?
Kenapa harus begitu?
Let's go.
Ayo.
Xueyan
Xueyan.
This is a family matter for the Liu family.
Ini adalah urusan keluarga Liu kalian.
It's not appropriate for outsiders like us to interfere.
Kami orang luar juga tidak bisa ikut campur.
You should handle it yourself.
Kau urus sendiri.
Grandma Mu, Huiming
Nenek Mu, Kak Hui Ming,
Please listen to my explanation.
Kalian dengarkan penjelasanku.
That's enough from you.
Cukup!
Mom
Ibu.
Mom, please help me again.
Ibu, bantulah aku lagi.
You stupid girl!
Dasar kau!
Mom
Ibu
You actually hit me!
Kau memukulku?
If I don't hit you,
Aku tidak memukulmu.
you'll never come to your senses in this lifetime.
Kau tidak akan sadar seumur hidup.
You've really disappointed me.
Benar-benar membuatku kecewa
Reflect on your actions.
Kau introspeksi diri dengan baik.
I'll take care of things at the police station.
Aku akan mengurus kantor polisi.
I'm so angry!
Menyebalkan.
Did I drink the wrong thing?
Jangan-jangan aku salah minum?
Cheers.
Bersulang.
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
Kepalaku agak pusing.
I'm going to the restroom.
Kamar mandi di sana.
That's absolutely impossible.
Tidak mungkin
It must be Lin Han.
Pasti Lin Han
It must be that bitch Lin Han's doing.
Pasti ulah Lin Han si murahan itu
Yinyin
Yinyin
What are you doing here?
Yinyin.
I'm not at the point where you can come and laugh at me.
Aku tidak akan sampai membuatmu menertawakanku.
No
Tidak.
It's not like that.
Bukan begitu.
Yinyin
Yinyin.
I feel sorry for you.
Aku kasihan padamu.
I'm your mother.
Aku adalah ibumu.
What?
Apa?
I'm your mom.
Aku ibumu.
Alright
Sudahlah.
Let's eat quickly.
Cepat makan.
It's been a hectic day.
Hari ini sudah ribut seharian.
Xiaowan is almost starving.
Xiao Wan sudah sangat lapar.
Right?
Benarkan?
About what happened today,
Masalah hari ini
we really have to thank Xiaowan.
Untung ada Xiao Wan
Of course.
Tentu saja.
I can't just watch Uncle Ying be forced into a corner.
Aku tidak bisa melihat Paman Ying dipaksa ke Gunung Liang.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
I worked so hard to find a stepdad.
Aku bersusah payah mencari Ayah Permaisuri,
I can't let someone just take him away.
Tidak boleh diambil begitu saja.
Uncle Ying
Paman Ying.
I just saw Aunt Liu acting all sneaky.
Aku baru saja melihat Bibi Liu diam-diam
I don't know what she was saying to the waiter.
Tidak tahu apa yang dia katakan pada pelayan.
Aunt Lu, over these years,
Bibi Lu beberapa tahun ini
has really spoiled her a bit too much.
Memang sedikit terlalu memanjakan dia.
Don't worry.
Kau tenang saja.
With me here, your mom will be fine.
Ada aku, ibumu tidak akan ada masalah.
Sorry, sir.
Maaf, Tuan.
I really didn't mean to.
Aku benar-benar tidak sengaja.
There's a lounge upstairs.
Di atas ada ruang istirahat.
How about I have the butler take you upstairs
Bagaimana kalau aku minta pengurus rumah membawamu ke atas?
to use a hair dryer?
Tiup dengan pengering rambut.
Mom
Ibu.
It's him.
Itu dia.
It's okay.
Tidak apa-apa.
You go ahead.
Kau pergi saja dulu.
I'll wait for you here.
Aku menunggumu di sini.
Let's go.
Pergilah.
Mom, it's him.
Ibu, itu dia
You're not even afraid of him.
Kau tidak takut padanya?
Such petty tricks
Keterampilan kecil seperti ini,
aren't even worth my attention.
Ibu masih tidak menganggapnya serius.
Mr. Ying
Direktur Ying.
Sorry about earlier.
Maaf, tadi aku sudah membuatmu basah.
I got your clothes wet.
Aku sudah membasahi bajumu.
Let me offer this drink as an apology.
Ini anggap sebagai permintaan maaf.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Take me to my room.
Antar aku ke kamar.
I feel like I've had a bit too much to drink.
Aku merasa sedikit mabuk.
Alright, alright, I'll take you.
Baik, aku antar.
Huiming.
Kak Hui Ming.
Today is Grandma's big birthday.
Hari ini adalah ulang tahun Nenek.
Look, I bought this dress especially for today.
Kau lihat rok yang aku beli khusus,
Is it pretty?
Cantik tidak?
Cheers.
Bersulang.
This room is so hot.
Kamar ini panas sekali.
Yinyin.
Yinyin.
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
Kepalaku agak pusing.
I'm going to the restroom.
Ke kamar mandi.
Then hurry up.
Cepatlah.
I'll wait for you.
Aku menunggumu.
Hello?
Halo.
Mr. Ying.
Tuan Ying.
We've finished investigating the hotel surveillance you requested.
Cctv hotel yang kau inginkan sudah selesai kami selidiki.
We found that your housekeeper, Qin Yue'e,
Kami menemukan pengurus rumah kau, Qin Yue 'e,
entered that room afterwards.
Kemudian masuk ke kamar itu.
The two of them stayed in the room for a long time.
Mereka berdua tinggal di kamar untuk waktu yang lama.
Alright, thank you for your hard work.
Baik, terima kasih.
Qin Yue'e, Aunt Qin.
qin Yue E. -ibu Qin.
This is a photo of you when you were one month old.
Ini adalah fotomu saat bulan purnama.
You have a birthmark on your back.
Ada tanda lahir di punggungmu
Isn't that right?
Benar, 'kan?
I don't believe it.
Aku tidak percaya.
I'm Lu Xueyan's daughter.
Aku adalah putri Lu Xueyan.
I'm the eldest daughter of the Liu family.
Aku adalah Nona Besar Keluarga Liu.
Yin Yin.
Yinyin.
It's true.
Itu benar.
Back then,
Waktu itu,
I wanted you to have a good life.
Aku mengirimmu ke keluarga Liu
That's why I sent you to the Liu family.
Baru mengirimmu ke Keluarga Liu.
Then why are you coming to me now?
Jadi, kenapa kau mencariku sekarang?
What do you want?
Apa yang kau inginkan?
Money?
Uang.
You want money, is that it?
Kau mau uang, 'kan?
I have plenty of money.
Aku punya banyak uang
As long as you stay far away from me,
Asalkan kau pergi sejauh mungkin
I can give you as much as you want.
Aku akan memberikannya kepadamu.
I...
Aku...
I don't want money.
Aku tidak mau uang.
I just want you.
Aku hanya ingin kau menjadi milikku.
I don't want that.
Aku tidak mau.
Don't touch me with your filthy hands.
Jangan sentuh aku dengan tangan kotor.
I...
Aku...
Jin Xiaowan
Jin Xiaowan,
She went to the paternity testing center.
Dia pergi ke pusat tes DNA
She asked someone to verify the relationship between Lu Xueyan and Lin Han.
Meminta orang untuk mengidentifikasi hubungan Lu Xueyan dan Lin Han
So what?
Jadi kenapa?
Lin Han
Lin Han
I was the one who took her.
Aku yang mencurinya
After I took her,
Setelah aku mencurinya,
I handed her over to the Lin Yuan couple, who also came here to make a living.
Diberikan kepada pasangan Lin Yuan yang juga mencari nafkah.
After they got the child,
Setelah mendapatkan anaknya,
they immediately left Shanghai.
Dan langsung meninggalkan Shanghai.
No one expected
Tidak ada yang menyangka
that after so many years, she would return here.
Setelah bertahun-tahun, dia kembali ke sini lagi.
What?
Apa
If Lin Han comes back,
Jika Lin Han kembali
Lu Xueyan will definitely investigate the truth thoroughly.
Lu Xueyan pasti akan menyelidiki kebenarannya
At that time,
Pada saat itu,
I absolutely won't allow such a thing to happen.
Aku tidak akan membiarkan hal ini terjadi.
The mother and daughter
Ibu dan anak itu
must disappear.
Harus menghilang.
Miss
Nona.
Miss, are you buying vegetables?
Nona, beli sayur?
The New Year is almost here.
Sebentar lagi tahun baru.
Have you prepared the dishes for New Year's Eve dinner?
Apa hidangan makan malam tahun baru sudah disiapkan?
Tell me,
Beritahu aku,
what will happen next?
Apa yang akan terjadi selanjutnya.
Can I
Apakah aku
really change my fate?
Bisa mengubah nasib atau tidak,
I don't want anything else.
Aku tidak menginginkan apa pun.
I just want to spend more time with my daughter.
Aku hanya ingin menemani putriku lebih lama.
A little longer.
Lebih lama lagi.
Everything happens for a reason.
Semuanya memiliki takdir.
I came just to tell you.
Aku datang untuk memberitahumu.
Hello?
Halo.
Xiaowan's mom.
Ibu Xiao Wan.
I wanted to ask if something happened at home.
Ingin bertanya apakah ada masalah di rumah?
Xiaowan hasn't come to school yet.
Xiao Wan belum datang ke sekolah.
How is that possible?
Bagaimana mungkin?
She hasn't come.
Tidak datang?
That's impossible.
Tidak mungkin.
I clearly saw her enter the school myself.
Jelas-jelas aku melihatnya masuk sekolah.
Hello?
Halo.
This is Liu Yinyin.
Aku Liu Yinyin.
Mom.
Ibu.
It's me, Xiaowan.
Aku adalah Xiaowan.
Xiaowan.
Xiaowan.
Mom.
Ibu.
Small troubles might be avoided.
Hal kecil mungkin bisa dihindari.
But when big things happen, there's no way to escape.
Hal besar datang, tetap tidak bisa dihindari.
The price you pay for going against fate—
Apakah kau benar-benar bisa menerima
can you really accept it?
Sungguh bisa menerimanya?